<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<INFORMATION>
	
	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Abucay Church</NAME>
		<PLACE>PG57+9QV, Abucay, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>A 17th-century Baroque church. The parish church, established in 1587 and administered by the Dominican Missionary Friars in 1588, is dedicated to Saint Dominic of Guzman.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Camaya Coast</NAME>
		<PLACE>Sitio wain, Mariveles, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>A once secluded cove, accessible to local fishermen, is now transformed into a prime leisure beach resort and residential development. With lush mountains, endless sunsets, and pristine beaches.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Death March Marker</NAME>
		<PLACE>CFPR+79X, Ave of the Philippines, Mariveles, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>Death March Marker was the starting point of the Bataan Death March in Bagac in 1942. A similar marker can be found in Mariveles. There are two (2) Zero Km. Death March Marker, one in the Free Port town of Mariveles and the other is in the beach town of Bagac, the largest town in Bataan.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Five Fingers</NAME>
		<PLACE>CFC8+PWF, Mawakis Cove Trail, Mariveles, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>This tourist attraction consists of five coves that look like actual fingers from a bird’s eye view, hence the name.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Laki Beach</NAME>
		<PLACE>Brgy. Biaan, Mariveles, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>A perfect spot to have quiet relaxation at the beach.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Las Casas</NAME>
		<PLACE>J95Q+XM3, Bagac, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>A famous Bataan tourist spot that lets you travel back in time. It features original old houses from different parts of the Philippines.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Mt. Natib</NAME>
		<PLACE>Brgy. Tala, Orani, Bataan.</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>Mount Natib is a dormant volcano standing at 1,253 meters above sea level with a difficulty level of 6/9.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Mt. Samat</NAME>
		<PLACE>Brgy. Diwa, Pilar, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>A memorial to all of the soldiers who died bravely in the battle against the Japanese forces and those who died during the Bataan Death March in World War II.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Mt. Tarak</NAME>
		<PLACE>GF3V+95C, Malaya, Mariveles, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>This Mariveles tourist spot offers a majestic view of the mountains and lets you connect with nature.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Balanga Wetland</NAME>
		<PLACE>Brgy. Tortugas, Balanga, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>This Balanga tourist spot has recorded about 35 species and 15 bird families.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>WWII Museum</NAME>
		<PLACE>MGJW+98X, Jose Basa St, City of Balanga, Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>This Bataan tourist attraction houses war memorabilia and dioramas, particularly those from the world-renowned Bataan Death March.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

	<ATTRACTIONS>
		<NAME>Playa La Caleta</NAME>
		<PLACE>J8MW+4FV, Matikis, Morong, 2108 Bataan</PLACE>
		<INFORMATION>Playa La Caleta (which means “Beach Cove”) or PLC for short, is an eco-tourism resort with a 100-hectare cove. it has a 1-kilometer white sand beach at the front, lush mountain jungle/forest in the middle and 3 waterfalls at the back. On the left side of the cove is also a 1-hectare islet, called Miguelito Island.</INFORMATION>
	</ATTRACTIONS>

</INFORMATION>